{
  "Burn Etiquette": {
    "Questions": {
      "nextPage": [ "Visa Application" ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "How many principles are there in the Code of the Republic?",
          "expectedAnswer": "11",
          "answers": [
            "10",
            "11",
            "12",
            "13"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Consent must be clearly granted.",
          "expectedAnswer": "True",
          "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Consent must be clearly granted.",
          "expectedAnswer": "True",
          "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "It is the responsibility of each participant to leave no trace at DeJā.",
          "expectedAnswer": "True",
          "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "You are encouraged to be a spectator.",
          "expectedAnswer": "False",
          "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  },
  "Survival Guide": {
    "The Beginner's Guide": {
      "Questions": {
        "nextPage": [ "Survival Guide", "The Basics" ],
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What is provided?",
            "expectedAnswer": "A location to gather",
            "answers": [
              "A location to gather",
              "Free WiFi",
              "Daft Punk at the trash fence"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "What isn't provided?",
            "expectedAnswer": "Garbage removal",
            "answers": [
              "Outhouses",
              "Garbage removal",
              "Some power"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "What should I expect?",
            "expectedAnswer": "Nothing",
            "answers": [
              "Fire",
              "Free WiFi",
              "Nothing"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Why do I need to register?",
            "expectedAnswer": "To get into DeJā",
            "answers": [
              "To get into DeJā",
              "To fly to Berlin"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Why are there no tickets sold?",
            "expectedAnswer": "DeJā is an experiment in commerce-free gatherings",
            "answers": [
              "DeJā is an experiment in commerce-free gatherings",
              "Printer cartridge's out of ink"
            ]
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "The Basics": {
      "Questions": {
        "nextPage": [ "Survival Guide", "Preparing" ],
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "Weather at DeJā is predictable.",
            "expectedAnswer": "False",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "The well at DeJā provides drinking water.",
            "expectedAnswer": "False",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "There is unlimited power for your use at DeJā.",
            "expectedAnswer": "False",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "There is a casual sound curfew between 6 and 9am.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Cell phone use is highly encouraged.",
            "expectedAnswer": "False",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Smoking is not allowed in the barn.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "If/When entering the kitchen, hands must be washed and sanitized.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Donations for covering expenses are accepted.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Those under 18 need to be accompanied by an adult.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Pets are welcome at DeJā.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "Preparing": {
      "Questions": {
        "nextPage": [ "Survival Guide", "Getting There" ],
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What will I need at DeJā?",
            "expectedAnswer": null,
            "answers": [
              "Water",
              "Food",
              "Camping gear",
              "Garbage bags",
              "Intoxicating aids",
              "Costumes",
              "Lighting"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "DeJā is a leave no trace event.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "It's okay to leave garbage laying around.",
            "expectedAnswer": "False",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "It is a good idea to leave space in your vehicle to take garbage with you when you leave.",
            "expectedAnswer": "True",
            "answers": [
              "True",
              "False"
            ]
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "Final Questions": {
      "nextPage": [ "Visa Application" ],
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "MOOP sweeps are highly encouraged.",
          "expectedAnswer": "True",
          "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "If someone asks you for directions, it is okay to share them even if they have not filled out a Visa.",
          "expectedAnswer": "False",
          "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  }
}
